Guide to the Paula Kamen Papers, 1970-2006 and undated (bulk 1991-2002) RL.00765
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials Series, 1990-2004 and undated, 13 boxes; About 550 items
  - Audio Cassettes, 1990-2004 and undated, 226 items
    - OR-171 Shedd, 1993 November 10 (2 of 2) (Box 85)
    - OR-172 S,, Maria (Box 85)
    - OR-173 S., Elizabeth/TeenVoices (Box 85)
    - OR-174 S., Valerie, 1993 October 26 (Box 85)
    - OR-175 Stephens, 1995 March 23 (Box 85)
    - OR-176 S., Paula, December 14 (Box 85)
    - OR-177 Tammy (Box 85)
    - OR-178 TCU (Box 86)
    - OR-179 TeenXpress (Box 86)
    - OR-180 T., Ann, 1993 November 20 (Box 86)
    - OR-181 T., Michael, 1993 October 18 (Box 86)
    - OR-182 Treveca (Box 86)
    - OR-183 Untitled 1 (Box 86)
    - OR-184 Untitled 2 (Box 86)
    - OR-185 Untitled 3 (Box 86)
    - OR-186 Untitled 4 (Box 86)
    - OR-187 Untitled 5 (Box 86)
    - OR-188 Untitled 6 (Box 86)
    - OR-189 Valene (Box 86)
    - OR-190 V of C (1 of 3) (Box 86)
    - OR-191 V of C (2 of 3) (Box 86)
    - OR-192 V of C (3 of 3) (Box 86)
    - OR-193 Virginia, 1992 September 15 (Box 86)
    - OR-194 Walsh (Box 86)
    - OR-195 Washington, D.C. interviews, 1993 April 23 (1 of 6) (Box 86)
    - OR-196 Washington, D.C. interviews, 1993 April 23 (2 of 6) (Box 86)
    - OR-197 Washington, D.C. interviews, 1993 April 23 (3 of 6) (Box 86)
    - OR-198 Washington, D.C. interviews, 18th Street, 1993 April 23 (4 of 6) (Box 86)
    - OR-199 Washington, D.C. interviews, 18th Street, 1993 April 23 (5 of 6) (Box 86)
    - OR-200 Washington, D.C. interviews, 18th Street, 1993 April 23 (6 of 6) (Box 86)
    - OR-201 W., Melanie, 2003 October 29 (Box 86)
    - OR-202 Weinberg (Box 86)
    - OR-203 Wendy and Craig, Washington, D.C. (Box 86)
    - OR-204 West Virginia (Box 86)
    - OR-205 Whitner, 1992 September 18 (Box 86)
    - OR-206 W., Nicole, 2003 December 6 (Box 86)
    - OR-207 Williams, pornography conference (Box 86)
    - OR-208 Wisconsin men, 1990 December 9 (1 of 2) (Box 86)
    - OR-209 Wisconsin men, 1990 December 9 (2 of 2) (Box 86)
    - OR-210 WOC Workshops (Box 86)
    - OR-211 Zibergeld/Playboy (Box 86)
    - OR-379 A., Mike, Santa Barbara 2 (Box 87)
    - OR-380 A., Mike, Santa Barbara 3 (Box 87)
    - OR-381 A., Mike, Santa Barbara 4 (Box 87)
    - OR-382 Doc Interviews, 1992 February 24 (Box 87)
    - OR-383 Hanton Copy, 1993 December 10 (Box 87)
    - OR-384 L., Barnie, 1991 September 23 (Box 87)
    - OR-385 Mackinnon, Catherine, 1993 September 28 (Box 87)
    - OR-386 P., Marianne, 1992 July 3 (Box 87)
    - OR-387 Nichols, July 8 (Box 87)
    - OR-388 NOW Conference, Chicago 1992 (Box 87)
    - OR-389 Plan 1 (Box 87)
    - OR-390 Pornography conference, June 24 (Box 87)
    - OR-391 Seventeen (1 of 2) (Box 87)
    - OR-392 Seventeen (2 of 2) (Box 87)
    - OR-393 Wheeling Class, November 26 (Box 87)
  - Compact Discs, 2004-2005, 7 items
    - OR-212 Book [All In My Head], 2004 February 24 (Box 93)
    - OR-213 Book [All In My Head], 2004 June 17 (Box 93)
    - OR-214 Book [All In My Head], 2004 July 24 (Box 93)
    - OR-215 Draft Grants CU, 2004 April 21 (Box 93)
    - [OR-216 removed from collection] (Box 93)
    - OR-217 Eight Forty-Eight, 2005 March 16 (Box 93)
    - OR-218 My Documents, 2004 March 18 (Box 93)
  - Micro Cassettes, 1993-1996 and undated, 127 items
    - OR-219 AMOCO (Box 88)
    - OR-220 AMOCO (Box 88)
    - OR-221 Amy (Box 88)
    - OR-222 Anthony (Box 88)
    - OR-223 Austin (1 of 4) (Box 88)
    - OR-224 Austin (2 of 4) (Box 88)
    - OR-225 Austin (3 of 4) (Box 88)
    - OR-226 Austin (4 of 4) (Box 88)
    - OR-227 Bea (Box 88)
    - OR-228 Becky (Box 88)
    - OR-229 Belli (1 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-230 Belli (2 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-231 Bridge (1 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-232 Bridge (2 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-233 Capless, 1993 July 16 (Box 88)
    - OR-234 Dawn (1 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-235 Dawn (2 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-236 Denton (1 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-237 Denton (2 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-238 Family & Work (Box 88)
    - OR-239 Franz (Box 88)
    - OR-240 Fred (Box 88)
    - OR-241 Gay & Kerry (Box 88)
    - OR-242 Gordon (Box 88)
    - OR-243 Griffin (Box 88)
    - OR-244 Gwen, UMASS (Box 88)
    - OR-245 Isadora (1 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-246 Isadora (2 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-247 LA Law (Box 88)
    - OR-248 Lesbians (Box 88)
    - OR-249 Mackie, San Francisco, 1994 July (Box 88)
    - OR-250 Mark (Box 88)
    - OR-251 Mills, UCLA (Box 88)
    - OR-252 Morph (Box 88)
    - OR-253 Nadia (Box 88)
    - OR-254 NARAL (Box 88)
    - OR-255 NCROW (Box 88)
    - OR-256 NOW (1 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-257 NOW (1 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-258 Patty (Box 88)
    - OR-259 Paul (1 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-260 Paul (2 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-261 Purdah (Box 88)
    - OR-262 Rutgers (Box 88)
    - OR-263 Ruth, 1994 January 14 (Box 88)
    - OR-264 Santa Cruz (1 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-265 Santa Cruz (2 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-266 Sarah (Box 88)
    - OR-267 Scratch (Box 88)
    - OR-268 Sherry (1 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-269 Sherry (2 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-270 Spencer, August 29 (Box 88)
    - OR-271 Starr (1 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-272 Starr (2 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-273 SUNY (Box 88)
    - OR-274 SUT, 1993 April 29 (Box 88)
    - OR-338 TWU, lesbians (1 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-339 TWU, lesbians (2 of 2) (Box 88)
    - OR-275 Untitled 1 (Box 88)
    - OR-276 Untitled 2 (Box 88)
    - OR-277 Untitled 3 (Box 88)
    - OR-278 Untitled 4 (Box 88)
    - OR-279 Untitled 5 (Box 88)
    - OR-280 Untitled 6 (Box 88)
    - OR-281 Untitled 7 (Box 88)
    - OR-281 Untitled 8 (Box 88)
    - OR-283 Untitled 9 (Box 88)
    - OR-284 Untitled 10 (Box 88)
    - OR-285 Untitled 11 (Box 88)
    - OR-286 Untitled 12 (Box 88)
    - OR-287 Untitled 13 (Box 88)
    - OR-288 Untitled 14 (Box 88)
    - OR-289 Untitled 15 (Box 88)
    - OR-290 Untitled 16 (Box 88)
    - OR-291 Untitled 17 (Box 89)
    - OR-292 Untitled 18 (Box 89)
    - OR-293 Untitled 19 (Box 89)
    - OR-294 Untitled 20 (Box 89)
    - OR-295 Untitled 21 (Box 89)
    - OR-296 Untitled 22 (Box 89)
    - OR-297 Untitled 23 (Box 89)
    - OR-298 Untitled 24 (Box 89)
    - OR-299 Untitled 25 (Box 89)
    - OR-300 Untitled 26 (Box 89)
    - OR-301 Untitled 27 (Box 89)
    - OR-302 Untitled 28 (Box 89)
    - OR-303 Untitled 29 (Box 89)
    - OR-304 Untitled 30 (Box 89)
    - OR-305 Untitled 31 (Box 89)
    - OR-306 Untitled 32 (Box 89)
    - OR-307 Untitled 33 (Box 89)
    - OR-308 Untitled 34 (Box 89)
    - OR-309 Untitled 35 (Box 89)
    - OR-310 Untitled 36 (Box 89)
    - OR-311 Untitled 37 (Box 89)
    - OR-312 Untitled 38 (Box 89)
    - OR-313 Untitled 39 (Box 89)
    - OR-314 Untitled 40 (Box 89)
    - OR-315 Untitled 41 (Box 89)
    - OR-316 Untitled 42 (Box 89)
    - OR-317 Untitled 43 (Box 89)
    - OR-318 Untitled 44 (Box 89)
    - OR-319 Untitled 45 (Box 89)
    - OR-320 Untitled 46 (Box 89)
    - OR-321 Untitled 47 (Box 89)
    - OR-322 Untitled 48 (Box 89)
    - OR-323 Untitled 49 (Box 89)
    - OR-324 Untitled 50 (Box 89)
    - OR-325 Untitled 51 (Box 89)
    - OR-326 Untitled 52 (Box 89)
    - OR-327 Untitled 53 (Box 89)
    - OR-328 Untitled 54 (Box 89)
    - OR-329 Untitled 55 (Box 89)
    - OR-330 Untitled 56 (Box 89)
    - OR-331 Untitled 57 (Box 89)
    - OR-332 Untitled 58 (Box 89)
    - OR-333 Untitled 59 (Box 89)
    - OR-334 Untitled 60 (Box 89)
    - OR-335 Untitled 61 (Box 89)
    - OR-336 Untitled 62 (Box 89)
    - OR-337 Untitled 63 (Box 89)
    - OR-394 Untitled 64 (Box 89)
    - OR-395 Untitled 65 (Box 89)
    - OR-396 Untitled 66 (Box 89)
    - OR-397 Untitled 67 (Box 89)
    - OR-340 Winthrop, 1996 March 26 (Box 89)
    - OR-341 Yard (Box 89)
  - Photographs, 1993, 1999, and undated, About 150 items (Box 93)
  - Videotapes, 1990-2004, 37 items
    - OR-342 20/20 Duke Men Acting for Change, Campus Rape (Box 90)
    - OR-343 [Bevery Hills] 90210, date rape, 1993/11 (Box 90)
    - OR-344 Arcenio, Future Sex (Box 90)
    - OR-345 Art Beat, 1998 November 12 (Box 90)
    - OR-346 The Brokaw Report, The Lost Generation, 1993 July 28 (Box 90)
    - OR-347 Dreamworlds: Desire/Sex/Power in Sex Video, 1990 (Box 90)
    - OR-348 Felicity, sex episode, 1999 January 19 (Box 90)
    - OR-349 Female Sexuality, The Learning Channel, 2000 December 2 (Box 90)
    - OR-350 Good Day Portland, Paula Kamen, 2004 March 14 (Box 90)
    - OR-351 How To Strip for Your Husband, The Self Discovery Series for Women (Box 90)
    - OR-352 If These Walls Could Talk (Box 90)
    - OR-353 Jane by Paula Kamen, Chopin Studio Theater, Chicago, IL, 1999 October 15 (Box 90)
    - OR-354 Jane Pratt Show, Paula Kamen (Box 90)
    - OR-355 Jenny Jones, beauty (Box 90)
    - OR-356 Kamen, Paula, Channel 5 News, 1997 (?) (Box 90)
    - OR-357 Kamen, Paula, Fox TV News, Chicago, 2000 November 4 (Box 91)
    - OR-358 Kamen, Paula, Lewis & Clark College, keynote speech, 2002 March 14 (Box 91)
    - OR-359 Lewinsky, Monica, 1999 March 3 (Box 91)
    - OR-360 Michigan Head, Pain, and Neurological Institute (Box 91)
    - OR-361 Music Television, Sex 1993 August 15, Real World Vices, 1993 August 16 (Box 91)
    - OR-362 Music Television, Public Service Announcement on AIDS 1994 September 12, Sex Doc, 1994 September 14 (Box 91)
    - OR-363 Music Television, More Sex in the 90s, 2000 January (Box 91)
    - OR-364 Music Television, 2001 May 9 (Box 91)
    - OR-365 Music Television, 1994 September 16, Boys Will Be Boys, Melrose Place, 1994 September 19 (Box 91)
    - OR-366 Music Television, obscene female rappers, 1996 November 25 (Box 91)
    - OR-367 Oprah, sex and generations (Box 91)
    - OR-368 Oprah, date rape, 1996 September 19 (Box 91)
    - OR-369 Public Service Announcement, Salt 'n Pepa, 1993 (Box 91)
    - OR-370 Real World, abortion episode, gay episode, 1993 (Box 91)
    - OR-371 Real World, 1993 (Box 91)
    - OR-372 Sally Jesse Rafael, Hooters, Operation Rescue, harassers, 1993 October 11 (Box 92)
    - OR-373 Seven Dates with Seven Writers: A New Unromantic Comedy, 1998 September 6 (Box 92)
    - OR-374 Springer, 1995 (Box 92)
    - OR-375 Streisand (Box 92)
    - OR-376 Take Back the Night, a documentary by Jenai Lane (Box 92)
    - OR-377 Tipped Uterus (Box 92)
    - OR-378 Tori Amos, 1996 April (Box 92)
- Printed Materials, 1992-1999, 20 items
  Items in this series consist of 20 issues of the magazines Deneuve and Curve. Other magazines and a number of zines are filed separately, with the Bingham Center's Women's, Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Movements Periodical Collection, and with the Bingham Center's Women's Zine Collection, respectively. A complete list of these titles maybe found in the Items Separated section below.
  - Curve, Volume 6, 3-6 (Box 93)
  - Curve, Volume 7, 1-4 (Box 93)
  - Curve, Volume 8, 3 (Box 93)
  - Curve, Volume 9, 4-5 (Box 93)
  - Deneuve, Volume 2, 3, 5-6 (Box 93)
  - Deneuve, Volume 3, 1, 4, 6 (Box 93)
  - Deneuve, Volume 4, 4, 6 (Box 93)
  - Deneuve, Volume 5, 1 (Box 93)